yamli.com 2011-06-07

# Yamli Privacy Policy

##  Yamli.com Privacy Policy 

Last updated: May 20, 2010 

Your privacy is very important to us. This document explains the types of information we collect while you use our services. I also details what we do and do not do with the information. 

###  What information does Yamli collect? 

  * When you type in an Yamli text box, your input is sent to our servers where it is converted to Arabic and sent back to your browser. As a result, our server logs contain the words and characters that you type while visiting Yamli. This is an inevitable consequence of the complex nature of the system used to convert your input to Arabic. 
  * Our logs also contain information about the IP address of your computer, the type of browser you are using, the time of your usage, your browser's language, and the url of the website you may have come from to reach yamli.com. 
  * In addition, Yamli uses cookies to anonymously identify returning users. 

###  How does Yamli use the collected information? 

  * Yamli may analyze the collected information to help improve the quality of its services. 
  * Yamli may display advertising customized to the information collected from your usage of the web site. 
  * Yamli may use information collected about your past activity to provide you with better results and/or customized content. 
  * Yamli may sell or otherwise provide access to the collected information to third parties for their business use, but such third party access and use must be consistent with Yamli's obligation to respect your privacy as described below. 

###  How does Yamli respect my privacy? 

  * Yamli respects your anonymity in all its uses of the collected information. 
  * Yamli will not disclose any personal information to third parties, with limited exceptions including compliance with legal processes and ensuring the security and availability of our services. "Personal information" is information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information by Yamli. 
  * Yamli may disclose non-personal information to third parties. 

###  External Links 

  * Yamli may provide links to external web sites operated by third parties. This privacy policy does not cover what these third parties do with the information they collect. 

Note: This privacy policy is subject to change. You are encouraged to check this page for possible updates.
